{
    "subject": "resource/Denis_Perger",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Denis Perger",
    "human_readable": "The label of Denis Perger is Denis Perger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9201774597167969,
            "question": "Who is Denis Perger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8938074111938477,
            "question": "What is the name of Denis Perger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8778247833251953,
            "question": "Is Denis Perger a known person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8221957683563232,
            "question": "Is there anything notable about Denis Perger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7723153829574585,
            "question": "Is Denis Perger a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474137544631958,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Denis Perger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.747378945350647,
            "question": "Does the name Denis Perger have any specific meaning?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.74068683385849,
            "question": "What field might Denis Perger be associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7294327616691589,
            "question": "Are there any famous people with the same name as Denis Perger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7121002674102783,
            "question": "Could you find any information about Denis Perger online?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Denis Perger is Denis Perger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1560_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people with the same name as Denis Perger?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1560_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field might Denis Perger be associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1560_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the name Denis Perger have any specific meaning?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1560_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1560_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, the name \"Denis Perger\" is mentioned multiple times as a football player. The label \"Denis Perger\" is indeed the correct label for this entity, given the context of the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The label of Denis Perger is Denis Perger\" is correct according to the context provided, as all documents refer to a player named Denis Perger without any contradiction."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}